你是谁
So who are you?
我们收到你的警报了 在哪
we got your alert. Where's...
那不是凯特琳
That's not Caitlin.
怎 怎么回事
What's- - what's happening here?
事实上 这是一个很长很令人困惑的故事
Actually, it's kind of a long and very confusing story.
不过我们很乐意分享
One which we are happy to hafe.
首先 请认识一下 你可以叫我斯诺
First, please meet- - - You can call me Snow.
等等 意思是第三个斯诺姐妹吗
Wait, as in, like, the third Snow sister?
巴里 你还记得那次你发现
Barry, do you remember the time that you found out
凯特琳想要复活冰霜
Caitlin was trying to bring back Frost,
然后你毁了她的实验室吗
and you destroyed her lab?
我没得选
- I didn't have a choice.
重点是
The point is,
凯特琳没有放弃
Caitlin never gave up.
她继续和我一起研究
She kept on working with me.
我们一起造了个机器 在凯特琳的身体里
Together, we built a machine to reactivate Frost's mind
重新激活了冰霜
in Caitlin's body.
-只有  -出了差错
Only Something went wrong.
代替凯特琳的是
But in place of Caitlin
是我
- I came out instead.
如果你不是凯特琳或冰霜
Well, if you're not Caitlin or Frost,
那你是谁
who are you?
说实话 我不知道
Honestly, I don't know.
我就像你们一样想知道我是谁
I wanna find out who I am just as much as the rest of you do.
这个斯诺完全是一张白纸
Snow here is a total blank slate
一点记忆没有
with zero memories.
所以我一直在尽力让她跟上进度
So I've been doing my best to bring her up to speed.
马克 凯特琳怎么了
Mark, what happened to Caitlin?
她在哪儿
Where is she?
凯特琳死了 巴里
Caitlin's dead, Barry.
-什么  -不可能
What? - That's impossible.
我知道你在想什么
- I- - I- - I know what you must be thinking,
但我有个让凯特琳复活的计划
but I have a plan to bring Caitlin back.
现在 冷冻舱应该从凯特琳身上提取了神经DNA
Now the CRC was supposed to unzip neural DNA from Caitlin.
这样我们就能把冰霜的脑信号
That way, we could isolate Frost's brain patterns
隔离在她体内 以后再下载到
inside of her- - - Download into another
另一个新的身体里
new body later on.
只是能量波动
Only a power fluctuation
导致了这个过程出了差错
caused the process to malfunction,
所以如果
and so if
闪电小队能给我提供稳定的能量来源
Team Flash could provide me with a stable energy source,
我们就能逆转这个过程
we could reverse the process
让凯特琳复活
and just bring Caitlin back.
所以现在你要我们帮忙了
So now you want our help?
是为了凯特琳
For Caitlin's sake,
对
yeah.
毕竟是凯特琳  我们必须试试
It's Caitlin. We have to try.
嗯 我被说服了
Yeah, I'm sold.
反正我们也没什么损失
What do we have to lose?
好的
Okay.
开工吧
Let's get to work.
我表现得怎么样
How did Ido? -
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
简直完美
You were perfect.
这比我们计划的要顺利
This is going better than we planned.
什么
What?
这就是凯特琳想要的
This is what Caitlin wanted.
当我们做宽这一切
And when we're done,
当我们做完这一切
冰霜会回来的
Frost will be back.
我不敢相信这真的发生了
- I can't believe this is really happening.
太疯狂了点
I mean, this is nuts.
确实
Yeah, I know, right?
尤其是
Especially with, uh,
就是最近发生的所有事
you know, everything else that's happened lately.
爱兰歌娜 听着 最近发生的事
Allegra, look, about what happened,
-我只是想让你知道  -我觉得我们应该先
I just want you to know- - - I think we should focus
专注凯特琳的事
on Caitlin first...
然后 等一切都结束了
and then, you know, when this is all done- -
啊对 你说得对
Uh, yeah, yeah, totally.
-我理解  -嗯
I get it. Yeah.
对
Right.
这一天天的
What a day.
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe it.
所以凯特琳消失了吗
So Caitlin's gone?
我知道
I know.
好难消化
It's too much- -
都好难消化
all of it.
宝贝 你没事吧
Babe, you okay?
巴里打电话来的时候 他说马克有办法
When Barry called, he said Mark has a plan
把凯特琳救回来
to get Caitlin back.
乔 这还不是我们唯一的麻烦
Joe, that is not even close to our only problem.
我想我们应该离开中城
- I think we should leave Central City.
塞西尔 我之所以
Cecile, the reason
说我们应该离开
I said we should leave
是因为我担心
is because I'm worried that
你的新能力越强
the stronger your new abilities become,
你就越会被推上前线
the more it puts you on the front line.
-哎呀  -当然
Come on- - - God knows
你可以处理好任何事情
you can handle anything,
但我还是担心会有谁想来伤害
but I'm still worried about who or what
我爱的女人
is coming after the woman I love
和我孩子的母亲
and the mother of my child.
这个家不能
This family can't
不能承受失去你
It can't handle losing you.
宝贝 我理解的
Babe, I get it.
真的
I do.
但你问我的是 我该如何在我们的家庭
But what you're asking me, how am I supposed to...
和整个城市的利益之间
choose between our family
做出选择
and the greater good of the entire city?
我该怎么选
How am I supposed to do that?
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do?
我不知道
- I don't know.
我真的很想去看看
I really wanted to see
老实泉
Old Faithful.
我们随时都可以去黄石公园
We can go to Yellowstone anytime.
现在 我们留在这里帮助
Right now, it's more important we stay here
马克更重要
to help Mark.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我很抱歉 我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
巴里
Barry- -
巴里 拜托
Barry, please.
是吗
Are you?
如果马克的计划不成功
If Mark's plan doesn't work
必须成功
- It has to.
我 我 我
*I, I, I, I*
我想要
*I feel like*
我想跳舞
*I feel like dancing*
请你喝一杯吧 帅哥
Buy you a drink, handsome?
我还在
One of us
上班呢
is still working.
我今晚一定会把月度最佳员工的徽章
I'll be sure to leave that Employee of the Month badge
放在你那半床上
on your side of the bed tonight.
可以关门了吗
Good to close up?
我可以让阿善堤关
I could get Ashanti to do it.
不行 我得自己挣钱养活自己
Ah, nah- - gotta earn my keep.
我听说老板特别混蛋
I hear the boss is a real jerk.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
-回家见  -好
See you at home. Okay.
我想跳舞
*I feel like dancing*
晚安
Good night.
如果你想找工作
if you're looking for a gig,
明天是业余之夜
amateur night's tomorrow.
我可不是外行 哈特利
I'm no amateur, Hartley,
而我已经有工作了
and I already have a gig
出来吧 哈特利
Aw, come on out, Hartley.
我保证我会很快
I promise to make it quick.
你只用
All you have to do is
听听音乐就好
listen to the music.
你是谁 你到底想干什么
Who are you, and what the hell do you want?
你可以叫我提琴手
You can call me The Fiddler,
我是来毁掉你的美好夜晚的
and I'm here to ruin your night.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你有我需要的东西
You have something I need.
哈特利
Hartleyl
Hartley.
告诉你老板我会回来的
Tell your boss I'll be back.
哈特利
Hartley!
没事的
- It's okay.
记住你是在做正确的事
Just remember you're doing the right thing.
我希望如此
- I sure hope so.
好 斯诺准备好了
AII right. Snow's ready.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我从没真正了解过她
I never really got to know her.
我们知道她非常勇敢
Well, we know she's brave as hell.
这需要多久
How long will this take?
需要多久就多久
Oh, as long as it needs to.
等等
Hold on.
神经传导率读数正在飙升
The neural conductivity readouts are surging.
马克 我们收到了超光速粒子反馈
Mark, we got tachyon feedback.
等等 有点不对劲
Hold on. Something's not right here.
你在搞什么
What the hell are you doing?
我是想救她的命
Trying to save her lifel
你不能打断这个过程
You can't interrupt this process!
你得马上把她放回去
You have to get her back inside right nowl
马克 切斯特 怎么了
Mark! Chester, what happened?
我不知道 我只是提供了
- I don't know. All I did was provide
一个稳定的电源 那是不会引发这个情况的
a stable power source. That wouldn't cause this.
他没说会疼
He didn't say this would hurt.
他只是说这会让她们复活
He just said it would bring them back.
她们
Them?
你是说凯特琳吗
You mean Caitlin?
不是
No.
她指的是凯特琳和冰霜
She means Caitlin and Frost.
马克 你所做的一切都是为了冰霜 对吧
Mark, everything you've done has been for Frost, hasn't it?
所以你才没提过她
That's why you haven't mentioned her.
这和凯特琳无关
This wasn't about Caitlin.
这是为了让冰霜复活
This was about bringing Frost back,
不是吗
wasn't it?
马克 不是吗
Mark, wasn't it?
凯 凯特琳不该
Cai- - Caitlin wasn't supposed
独自回来的 巴里
to come back alone, Barry.
她们都是
They both were.
天
God
试图将她们俩带回来
Trying to bring them both back,
导致了故障
that must've caused the malfunction.
只有这样才解释的通
It's the only thing that makes sense.
你为什么骗我们
Why did you lie to us?
因为我不能信任你们任何一个
Cause I can't trust any of you...
尤其是你 巴里
you most of all, Barry.
所以我们当初才不得不
That's why we had to build the CRC in secret
私底下建造了冷冻舱
in the first place,
因为凯特琳知道
because Caitlin knew that you
你公再次阻止她的
would try to stop her again
马克
Mark,
伙计 这样不对
man, this- this isn't right.
抱歉 闪电侠小队们
- I'm sorry, Team Flash.
就因为你们都放弃了冰霜
Just because you all gave up on Frost
不 等于我也可以
doesn't mean that I can.
我永远不能
I never will.
是马克吗
Is that Mark?
不是 是入侵者警告
No, it's an intruder alert.
实验室有人闯入
The med lab's been breached.
你留这
Stay here.
-哈特利  -凯特琳在哪
Hartley? - Where's Caitlin?
-我需要一个医生  -她走了
I need a doctor. - She's away.
声波 阻碍了我正常的心跳节奏
Soundwaves...short- circuiting my heart's natural rhythm,
我怎么 我是说
How do I I mean- -
用音速腕带
Use the sonic cuff.
-音速腕带  -最底下的抽屉
Sonic? - The bottom drawer!
底层抽屉
Bottom drawer!
给
There. -
你没事了吧
Are you good?
-还好吗  -怎么这么慢啊 艾伦
You okay? - Took you long enough, Allen.
抱歉 我不知道
- I'msorry. I mean, I didn't know- -
你说底层抽屉 但其实在顶层
you said the bottom drawer. It was in the top drawer.
我甚至不知道你
I didn't even know what you- -
无所谓了 让我休息一下
Never mind. Let me rest.
天
Oh, gosh.
心率失常短期好不起来
This arrythmia isn't going away anytime soon.
腕带只能缓解 不能治愈
Cuff's a patch, not a cure.
-好  -哈特利
Okay. Hartley?
是哈特利
- It's Hartley, yeah. It's...
你怎么进来的
How did you get in here,
你出了什么事
and what happened to you?
-首先 我过去在这工作  -太好了
One, I used to work here- Great.
第二 某个乐师精神病
And two, some musical psycho
用她的杀人小提琴袭击了我
attacked me with her murder violin- -
说她自己叫提琴手
calls herself The Fiddler.
就是她袭击了你吗
- Is this who attacked you?
她叫伊兹·鲍温
Her name is Izzy Bowen,
上次见面的时候我们成了朋友
only we were friends the last time we met.
不用因为我就不再跟伊兹做朋友了
Oh, well, no need to unfriend Izzy on my account.
不是她
It's not her.
巴里 两天出来俩坏人
Barry, that's two new Rogues in two days,
现在马克也在骗我们
and now Mark is lying to us too
天堂也有麻烦了
Trouble in paradise?
-拜托了  -别担心
Please. - Don't worry about it.
我来对付马克
I'lI handle Mark.
无聊
Bored.
唾觉
Sleeping now.
你的升级没起作用啊
Your upgrade didn't work.
别误会
Don't get me wrong.
我喜欢这小提琴
I love the fiddle and all.
你让我失望了
You failed me.
这就是代价
This is the price.
我不允许失败
Failing is not an option.
现在把我要的给我
Now bring me what I want,
否则下次你死定了
or next time, you die.
我说清楚了吗
Am I clear?
是的
Yes,
非常清楚
very.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
再来一轮
Another round.
算了 干脆来一整瓶吧
You know what? Just make it the whole bottle.
那也没办法带她回来
- It still won't bring her back.
我只是想谈谈
I just wanna talk.
你只是在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
你搞砸了 马克
And you screwed up, Mark- -
而且很严重
badly.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道你为什么这么做
- I know why you did it.
好吧
Okay.
你继续说教
No, go ahead. Enlighten me.
因为你全心全意的爱着冰霜
Because you loved Frost
现在还爱着
with all your heart. You still do.
有时候 当我们爱一个人很深时
Sometimes, when we love someone like that,
就会为了正确的理由
we do the wrong things
做出错误的事
for the right reasons.
我知道 我也这样过
I know I have.
拜托
Please.
你是说你不再生我气了吗
Are you saying you're not mad at me anymore?
不  我还在气
No, I am,
但我知道你为什么撒谎了
but I understand why you lied.
但有件事你也要明白
But there's something you need to understand now too:
我们该如何去做
how we operate.
你现在也是团队的一员
You are a part of this team now,
也就是说我们会支持你
and that means we have your back,
但你也要支持我们
but you need to have ours,
也就是说
which also means no more
不能再欺骗我们了
going rogue.
马克
Mark
如果你接受我们
If you let us in,
我们一起努力
we work together,
就能将不可能变成可能
we can do the impossible.
但我们必须团结一致
But we have to stick together.
我们得立刻走了
We have to go right now.
-去哪  -立刻
Go where? - Right now.
-哪啊  -快
Where? - Come on.
这也是团队合作之一吗
Is this, like, one of those team things?
什么叫这永远不能成功
What do you mean this was never gonna work?
我对冷冻舱做了全面的诊断
- I ran a full diagnostic on the CRC,
试图弄清楚到底哪儿出了问题
trying to figure out what went wrong,
最后发现 神经DNA
and what I found was, neural DNA
无法释放冰霜的意识
could never unlock Frost's consciousness.
我们需要内源性神经印记来实现这一目标
We need endogenous neural imprints to make this work.
好吗
Okay?
但你说的是凯特琳的思维图谱
But you're talking about a literal map
我们去哪能找到
of Caitlin's mind. Where are we gonna find
这种东西呢
something like that?
托马斯·斯诺
Thomas Snow.
凯特琳的父亲
Caitlin's dad?
他死了
He's dead.
不 艾瑞斯说的对
No, Iris is right.
托马斯·斯诺将冰霜的意识
Thomas Snow attached Frost's consciousness
附到了儿时凯特琳的身上
to Caitlin when she was a child.
凯特琳在自己的公寓里
Caitlin downloaded everything she could find
将她能找到的所有电子文档都下载了
from his digital files at her apartment,
说纸质文件和其它所有的文件都存在
said that the hard copies and all the rest are in storage
坦豪斯的实验室 有很多 但是
at Tannhauser Labs. Now, it's a lot, but
我们在凯特琳家见
Meet me at Caitlin's.
我去问问坦豪斯实验室的卡拉
I'lI check in with Carla at Tannhauser.
切斯特 你和马克准备好冷冻舱
Chester, you and Mark get to work on the CRC.
等我们找到了所需的东西
Once we find what we're looking for,
就会把凯特琳还有冰霜
we're gonna bring back Caitlin
一起带回来
and Frost.
我已经把泛音输入了
I entered the harmonics already.
现在快点吧 我知道
Now, come on. I know this.
法拉克
Frak.
见鬼
Damn it
为什么不工作呢
Why aren't you working?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你是冰霜的另一个姐妹吧
Well, you're obviously the other Snow sister.
实际上我现在有点忙 你不介意吧
Actually, I'm kind of busy, if you don't mind.
你在忙什么
What are you working on?
我的声波手套
My sonic gauntlets- -
关你啥事
why do you care?
我不是想管你的声波手套
Oh, I don't- about your gauntlets.
只是你刚才好像很疼
You just seemed like you were in pain.
出什么事了吗
What's wrong?
我的心率不稳定 极其危险
- I have a dangerously erratic heart rate
因为一个朋克女巫
due to some punk witch
在我不觉察的情况下袭击了我
who caught me with my guard down.
但下次就不会这样了
But that won't be a problem next time,
因为我要把我的手套功率提高
because I'm boosting my gauntlet's efficiency
百分之四百
by 400%.
为什么
Why?
算了 你别问了行吗
You know, actually, it doesn't matter.
就一边呆着去
If you could just, please, go away or something...
好吧
Okay,
我来问你哈
I'm gonna make this easy.
你有凯特琳·斯诺的
Do you have any of Caitlin Snow's
医疗知识吗
medical knowledge?
-没有  -没有哈
No. No, okay,
那你的手或者眼睛
um, can you shoot ice
能射出冰霜吗
from your hands or eyes?
随便哪都行
Either is acceptable.
-不能  -不能 那你就帮不到我
No. No- - then you can't help me,
所以你一点用都没有
and therefore, you are uselessl
所以我拜托你离开我吧
So please leave me alo-
你现在不应该再工作了
You shouldn't be working right now
或者生气的问别人一些奇怪的问题
or angrily asking people weird questions.
太烦心了
It's disturbing.
我必须弄好这个
I have to finish this.
你害怕有人会找到你吗
Are you scared that person will find you?
我相信巴里和其他人一定会
Because I'm sure Barry and the others have-
我得离开这 明白吗
I have to get out of here, okay?
如果我不
If I don't...
你不担心自己受伤
You're not afraid of getting hurt.
你担心其他人会受伤
You're afraid of someone else getting hurt.
你认为他们有危险
You think they're in danger.
所以我才
And that is why
必须要完成这件事
I have to finish these:
这样才能保证他安全
so I can keep him safe...
也是我唯一能做的
The only way that I can.
你要去杀了那个朋克女巫
You're going to kill the punk witch?
不 不行 杀戮是不对的
Oh, no. Killing is wrong.
中城的超能人类暴力事件
And Central City has more meta- violence per capita
要比其他城市都多
than any other city in the world.
你不是会杀人的那种人 我能看出来的
You're not a killer. I can tell.
你又不了解我
You don't know me.
其实 我可以很诚实的说
Actually- - and I can say this quite truthfully-
我觉得我了解你比了解自己都深
I think I know you better than I know myself.
之前我是个超能罪犯
- I used to be a meta- criminal,
像他们说的一样 是个恶棍
a Rogue, as they say.
我总会伤害别人
I used to hurt people all the time,
并乐在其中
and I enjoyed it.
是什么改变了你呢
What changed you?
是罗德里克 行了吗
Oh, Roderick, okay?
罗德里克
Roderick.
你为了保护他而做出了改变
You changed to keep him safe?
真是不错呢
That's beautiful.
但这并不等同于彻底的改头换面
But that's not real change,
对不对
is it?
为了你所爱的人而做出的改变
Deciding to change for the person you love
并不代表那就是你心之所向
doesn't mean you've decided who you wanna be.
那是个你要为你自己而做出的选择
That's a choice you still have to make for yourself,
对不对
isn't it?
拜托请告诉我
Please tell me
你有所发现
you found something.
我们得把凯特琳跟冰霜弄回来
We have to get Caitlin and Frost back.
做不到
We can't.
这是真的吗
- Is this really true?
我读了十几遍
- I read it a dozen times.
在他最初的实验中
In his original experiment,
托马斯·斯诺试图创造出个凯特琳2.0版
Thomas Snow tried to create a Caitlin 2. 0,
能对肌萎缩性脊髓侧索硬化症免疫的版本
one that would be immune to ALS,
但相反 他创造出了一个
but instead, he created a daughter
有两种混合意识的女儿
with two mixed consciousnesses,
当他试图逆转的时候
and when he tried to reverse it,
发现
he found out
逆转过程会杀掉二者之一
the process would kill one of them.
这也是托马斯从没建造自己冷冻舱的原因
That's why Thomas never built his own CRC,
因为他同时爱着凯特琳跟冰霜
because he loved both Caitlin and Frost.
他不忍心失去任何一个
He couldn't bear to lose either of them.
就像我们一样
Just like us.
巴里 要是斯诺进到了那台机器中
Barry, if Snow goes into that machine,
然后凯特琳跟冰霜只能回来一个
and only Caitlin or Frost can come back
我们得选择
We're gonna have to choose
带哪个回来
who to bring back.
凯特琳跟我说的最后一件事
You know, the last thing Caitlin said to me
就是她永远不会停止复活冰霜
was that she'd never stop trying to bring back Frost.
我们要尊重她的意愿 尊重她的计划
We need to honor her by honoring her plan.
马克 我们都清楚
Mark, we're all pretty clear
你的意见了 我想听听大家意见
on your opinion. I wanna hear everybody else's.
好吧
Okay.
我支持复活冰霜
I vote to bring back Frost
马克说的对
Mark's right
凯特琳帮我们选好了
Caitlin chose for us.
这本就是她的计划 所以选择冰霜就是尊重她
This was her plan, so choosing Frost honors her.
对不对 查克
Right, Chuck?
查克
Chuck?
不好意思 但是
sorry, but, uh,
不是
but no.
爱兰歌娜 当初死亡风暴把我爸复活
Allegra, look, when Deathstorm brought my dad back,
教会了我一件事
it taught me one thing:
就是复活死者
that resurrecting the dead
是反自然的
is unnatural.
现在 我不想选
Now, I don't wanna choose,
但非让我选的话
but if I have to,
我选择凯特琳
I'd choose Caitlin,
因为从科学层面上来说
cause when I run through the science,
这样才是最合理的
it's what makes the most sense to me.
二比一
it's two to one.
我猜猜
Let me guess:
你支持切斯特对不对
you're with Chester, right?
这样 你的超级老公就能跟你一起选凯特琳了
That way, your super- hubby can tip tl e scales to Caitlin.
不是 我选择冰霜
Uh, no I choose Frost.
我有自己的理由 但这就是我想选的
I have my reasons, but that's how I feel.
那就是三比一了
Well, it's three to one.
我需要多些时间考虑一下
I just need more time to think about it.
想考虑多久都随你 老大
Well, think about it all you want, boss man,
但八小时之后 我就动手了
but in eight hours, I'm doing this,
不管你同不同意 如果你想阻止我
with or without you, and if you try to stop me,
后果出了什么事都只能怪你自己
you'll have no one but yourself to blame for the fallout.
他可以怪我
He can blame me.
你们是一家人
You all are a family.
现在却出现分歧 这都是我的错
Now you're being torn apart, and it's all my fault?
我希望自己从没出生过
I wish I'd never been born.
有史以来最烂的一天
Worst day ever.
斯诺错了
Snow is wrong.
不是她的错
It's not her fault.
是我的
It's mine.
在我摧毁凯特琳实验室之前
The last thing I said to Caitlin
跟她说的最后一句话是
before I destroyed her lab was,
对不起
I'm sorry. "
事实上 我并不觉得抱歉
The truth is, I wasn't.
巴里 我之所以选择冰霜
Barry, the reason that I chose Frost
是因为第一次在我有机会的时候
was because I didn't choose her the first time,
我没有选她
when I had the chance.
这也是我选择复活冰霜的原因
That's why I chose to bring Frost back:
因为她活着的时候 我并没有选择她
because I didn't choose her when she was alive.
怎么了
What is it?
凯特琳踏入冷冻舱的那一刻
The moment Caitlin stepped
她已经做出了决定
into the CRC, she made her own choice
决定自己想要什么
about what she wanted,
自己想成为谁
who she wanted to be.
要我们一直以来
And what if we've been
都想错了呢
thinking about this all wrong?
我知道我们要做什么了
I know what we need to do.
你好
Hello.
你叫 斯诺 对吧
It's, uh, Snow, right?
塞西尔
Cecile,
超能人类律师
meta- human attorney
以及超能人类英雄
and meta- human superhero.
马克跟我提起过你
Mark told me all about you.
你喜欢这个天气吗
You enjoying the weather?
我喜欢下雨
I love the rain.
我喜欢大自然所有现象
I love all of nature.
会让我感觉
It just- - it makes me feel so
很平静
at peace.
是 能看出来
Yeah, I can see that.
这是因为自然万物都有其目的
- It's because everything in nature has a purpose.
就像你一样 你也有目的
just like you. You have a purpose.
你会帮助别人
You help people.
我只是
I just
我希望知道自己的目的是什么
I wish I knew what my purpose was.
感觉很奇怪
It's strange.
现在 我感觉自己跟所有生物都紧密相连
Right now, I feel so connected to all living things,
却又如此孤立
and yet so disconnected
无援
and alone.
你知道你是第一个
Do you know that you're the first person
我读不懂你感受的人吗
whose feelings I can't read?
一般来说
Usually,
出现这种情况我会担心
ooh, that is something I'd be worried about,
但现在却说不好了
but I don't know.
这次并没有担心
Not this time.
不知怎么了 你给人感觉就像个朋友
Somehow, you just seem like a friend.
那咱们就做朋友吧
Then let's be.
朋友
Friends.
很好笑吗
Was that funny?
我是个有意思的人吗
Am I a funny person?
那就太好了
That would be nice.
你是个很真诚的人
You are very genuine,
这种人很罕见的
and that is rare.
谢了
Thanks.
我听说其他队员
So I heard about what the rest of the team
投票的事了
was voting on.
我得跟你说
I gotta tell ya.
讲真 我不清楚如果自己在场
I honestly don't know how I would've voted,
会投给谁 乔会投给谁
had I been there, or Joe.
所以
So...
我想问你个问题  一般来说这问题不需要问的
I'm gonna ask you a question that I usually don't have to.
你现在感觉如何
How are you feeling right now?
尽管我的存在
Even though my entire existence
就是个谜
is a mystery,
首先 不管我是谁
one, whoever I am,
我喜欢我自己
I like myself,
其次
and two...
我不想回到那个金属盒子里去
I don't wanna go back inside that metal box.
现在我很担心大家
And now I'm afraid of the decision
会做出什么决定
the team will make.
你应该自己来做决定
You should make the decision for yourself.
-真的吗  -真的
Really? Yeah.
我们看了托马斯关于冰霜跟斯诺的
We looked at Thomas'original files
原始档案
on Frost and Snow.
冰霜被创造出来的时候
When Frost was created,
托马斯没有擅自决定他女儿应该是谁
Thomas didn't try to decide who his daughter should be.
他后退了一步 让她们自行决定
He took a step back, and he let'em figure it out.
所以使用冷冻舱选择你应该是谁
So using the CRC and choosing who you should be,
这不是由我们决定的
that's not our choice to make.
只有你自己才能觉得要成为谁
Only you can decide who you're gonna be.
行吧 那我们就这么办了
Ooh, okay, this is what we're doing.
轮到我了
Okay, my turn.
你做出决定了吗
So you've made a decision?
还没
Not even,
但不管我做出什么决定
but whatever decision I make,
都是我自愿的
it'll be mine...
纯自愿
all mine.
怎么了
What is it?
市中心发生了大规模的声波袭击
- It was a massive sonic attack downtown.
应该是我们的提琴手朋友回来
It looks like our Fiddler friend is back
准备大干一场了
and ready to rumble.
等下 那里是哈特利的喀拉喀托俱乐部
Wait, that's Hartley's Krakatoa Club.
他去找提琴手了
He's gone after The Fiddler.
可他伤还没好 为什么不找人帮忙
- If he's still hurt, why didn't he ask for help?
他不想你们帮忙
He doesn't want your help.
他终于做了决定
He finally made his choice.
我看着像是开玩笑吗
Does it look like I'm playing?
最后问一次 哈特利·拉维在哪儿
For the last time, where is Hartley Rathaway?
-拜托  -放他走
Please Let him go.
哈特利
Hartley.
我就知道 如果我不断给你施压的话
I knew, if I put the squeeze on your squeeze,
你迟早是会现身的
you'd show up sooner or later.
来得也挺及时 因为我已经开始厌倦
Just in time, too, cause I was starting to get bored
折磨你的手下了
of torturing your employees.
她把他们全杀了
She killed them all
全部雇员
the whole crew.
我有说过
Did I mention
还有生不如死的命运吗
that there are fates worse than death?
结束了 提琴手
- It's over, Fiddler.
你无能为力
You're powerless
又寡不敌众
and outnumbered.
闪电侠
Oh, Flash.
你来看我的演出了
You came to my show.
你看 乐器只是工具而已
See, instruments are just a tool.
真正的艺术家会使用自身的能力
A real artist uses what's inside them
是时候达到我的此行目的了
Time to get what I came for.
你喜欢我的升级吗
How do you like my upgrade?
不要 住手
Don't. Stop
斯诺告诉了我你说的话
Snow told me what you said.
你不必这样做的
You don't have to do this.
你还可以另选出路
You can still choose another way.
太晚了
It's too late.
她把罗德里克害死了
Roderick is dead because of her.
我现在没有生活的目标了
I have nothing to live for now.
你还有的
Yes, you do.
我给你看
I'lI show you.
提琴手没有杀死他们
The Fiddler didn't kill them.
他们被困在一个震动相里
They're trapped in a vibrational phase.
可是需要你的手套救他们出来
But they need your gauntlets to get them out.
你做了正确的选择
You made the right choice.
并在此过程中重置了一些东西
And reset things in the process.
你今天救了很多人命
You saved a lot of lives today
你打算怎么处置提琴手
What do you wanna do with The Fiddler?
你自己做主
You figure it out.
我没空
I'm busy.
看看他
Aw, look at hfm,
像只迷路的流浪狗一样四处游荡
wandering around like a lost puppy.
你还好吗
You all right there?
不好 我们达到了此行目的
No. We got what we came for.
现在赶紧离开这里
Now let's get the hell out of here.
是莫瑟
- It was Mercer.
他带走了提琴手
He took The Fiddler.
还有我的手套
And my gauntlets.
她叫安德里亚·沃泽克
Her name is Andrea Wozzeck.
原来她也在跟欧文·莫瑟合作
Turns out she's also working with Owen Mercer.
大家都不知道原因
Why is anyone's guess.
超级坏蛋也组队了 这下好了
Supervillain team- up, great.
他们为什么想要哈特利的手套呢
So do we know why they want Hartley's gauntlet?
-这重要吗  -呃
Do we care? - Uh
我现在最关心的是
Look, the only thing that I'm concerned about right now
你是怎么决定的
is, "What did you decide?
我没做任何决定
I didn't decide anything.
是斯诺决定的
Snow did.
她已经告诉了其他人
She already told everybody else.
是时候也告诉你了
I guess now it's time she tells you too.
那怎么
What is.
我知道你一直过得很不好
- I know that this has been difficult for you,
不管我作何决定 都会对你产生巨大影响
and that whatever decision I make will affect you a lot,
可是都比不上对我的影响
but not as much as it will affect me
这是我的命运
This is my fate,
我的未来
my future,
我的生活
my life.
我不要回到冷冻舱里去
I'm not going back inside the CRC.
什么
What?
我要走自己的路
- I'm gonna choose my own path
过自己的生活
and be my own person,
不管这条路通往哪里
whoever that ends up being.
就这样吗
That's it?
难道我就该忘掉冰霜
What, I'm just supposed to forget about Frost
-接受这一切吗  -对
and accept this? - Yes,
因为这不是我的选择
because I didn't choose this.
是凯特琳的选择
Caitlin did
她创造了一个人
when she created a person
一个富有感情
with feelings
有自由意志的人
and free will,
我不会放弃这一切
and I won't give that up
去成为另一个人
to become someone I'm not.
拜托 你自己连个名字都没有
Please, you don't even have your own name.
其实我有的
Actually, I do.
我今天才发现 父亲一直梦想着
I found out today that my father always dreamed
创造新事物
of creating something
或者新生命
or someone new,
他取名为喀俄涅
and he called her Khione.
科学犹如大自然
But science is like nature.
可以很残酷
It can be cruel
也可以很美丽
as well as beautiful.
不管怎样 我们都控制不了
Either way, we can't control it.
我知道凯特琳和冰霜已经消失了
So I know Caitlin and Frost are gone,
我们可以悼念藤蔓上
and we can mourn the flowers
凋零的花朵
that have fallen from the vine,
但是我们不能要求新开的骨朵
but we can't ask a new bloom
放弃自己的生命来挽回之前的鲜花
to give up its place in exchange.
希望你能够接受这一点
I hope you can accept that.
希望你能够接受我
I hope you can accept me,
因为我想活下去
cause I'd like to live
跟你们所有人一起成长
and grow with all of you.
我们也希望这样
We want that too.
你必须马上进去 好吗
You need to get inside right now, okay?
这是我们的计划 一直以来的计划
That was always the plan. That was our plan.
那是凯特琳的计划
That was Caitlin's plan!
计划有变
Plans change.
你知道自己刚干了什么蠢事吗
Do you realize what you've just done?
知道
Yeah.
帮助了一位新朋友
I just helped a new friend.
下次等我见到你
The next time that I see you,
一定要把你拿下
I am taking you down.
马克
Mark
看来你已经完全恢复了
Looks like you're back to 100%.
雨停了
- It stopped raining.
马克会好起来吗
- Is Mark gonna be okay?
希望会吧
I hope so.
阳光明媚
Well, the sun is shining,
我们坚持了一周
and we made it through the week.
而且毫发无损
Mm, and in one piece at that.
尽管很难相信
And even though it's hard
我们再也见不到
to believe that we'll never see
凯特琳或者冰霜了
Caitlin or Frost again,
我还是替喀俄涅高兴
I am happy for Khione.
我知道你的意思
Yeah, I know what you mean.
所以我一直告诉自己
That's why I keep telling myself that
冰霜自愿成为地狱冰霜与死亡风暴战斗
Frost chose to become Hellfrost and fight Deathstorm,
就像凯特琳自愿进入冷冻舱
just like Caitlin chose to go into the CRC,
现在喀俄涅也做了自己的选择
and now Khione's made her choice too.
对
Yeah.
我觉得新版凯特琳
Is it crazy to think that this
就是她一直想成为的样子
new version of Caitlin is what
这想法荒谬吗
she would've wanted all along?
一点也不
No, not at all.
我觉得她会喜欢这个自己的
I think she'd like her.
那么
So?
周末有什么计划吗
Got any weekend plans?
其实我在想
Actually, I was thinking
我们可以去看间歇泉
we could take in a geyser.
坐在这里 吞噬我的内心 等待
*Sittin'here, eatin'my heart out, waitin'*
等待爱人的到来
*Waitin'for some lover to come*
拨了无数个号码
*Dialed about a thousand numbers*
你真会跳舞
You are a great dancer!
乔真会站着不动
And Joe is very good at standing stilll
你真幽默
You are funny!
我需要一些热辣恋人 宝贝 今晚
*I need some hot stuff, baby, tonight*
我需要一些热辣恋人 今晚
*Iwant some hot stuff, baby, this evening*
必须有热辣恋人
*Gotta have some hot stuff*
今晚必须有热辣恋人
*Gotta have some love tonight*
热辣
*Hot stuff*
各大应用商店皆可下载
我需要热辣恋人
*I need hot stuff*
各大应用商店皆可爪载
查克
Chuck!
各大应用商店皆可下载
我需要热辣恋人
*I want some hot stuff*
各大应用商店皆可下载
要跳舞吗
Wanna dance?
各大应用商店皆可下载
我需要热辣恋人
*I need hot stuff*
各大应用商店皆可下载
宝贝 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝
*Baby, baby, baby, baby*
各大应用商店皆可下载
今晚
*Tonight*
最棒的蜜月冒险
Best babymoon adventure- -
史无前例
Ever.
我爱你 韦斯特·艾伦太太
- I love you, Mrs. West- Allen.
我爱你
- I love you.
尽管你舞技超差
even if you are a terrible dancer.
拜托
Oh, come on.
我要热辣恋人 宝贝 今晚
*I want some hot stuff, baby, this evening*
我舞技超好的
I'm a good dancer.
你瞧好了
Yeah, watch this.
好吧
Okay.
准备好了
- It's ready.
中城市民们 闪电侠让我颜面扫地
Central City, The Flash disgraced me.
现在你们所有人
Now a of you
都要为此付出代价
will pay the price,
正义将得到伸张
and justice wil be served
and justice will be served.
别扫我的兴
*Don't kill my vibe*
我简直完美无缺
*I'm flawless by design*
看看我
Me, look at me.
-嗯 上道了  -没人会跳这些动作
Yeah, you got it- Nobody else has these moves.
-你看  -那其实不算
Look. - That's not really...
我喜爱跳舞
- I love dancing!
SIMON SMITH
他是闪电侠
He's The Flash!
RICK STRANAN
-不 我不漏   -开玩笑
Nope, no, I'm notl Just kidding!
GFGdLIVSBC
我天生就是舞者
*I was born for this! *
OCR by China_sky
翻译：擦枪字幕组